[{"question": " okay!  this is it!  we're gonna get married!", "answer": " are you sure you wanna do this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " whoa!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  come on pheebs! hurry! hurry! hurry! hurry!", "answer": " okay! okay! okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  n-no running in the chapel!", "answer": "  hey! don&#146;t you give me any of your&#151;hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " what are you guys doing here?", "answer": " ross and rachel left us a message saying they were getting married! isn&#146;t that why you guys are here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yes! well that-yes.", "answer": " why else would we be here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " well! what happened?! did we miss it?", "answer": " we actually missed it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, maybe you wouldn&#146;t have had you  run in the chapel!", "answer": " this is insane!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " what&#146;s the big deal, y&#146;know? it&#146;s not like it&#146;s a real marriage.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, if you get married in vegas, you&#146;re only married in vegas.", "answer": " what are you talking about? if you get married in vegas you&#146;re married everywhere.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  really?!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh my god!&#151;eh! well&#133;", "answer": " in case you haven&#146;t heard, courteney cox got married to david arquette during hiatus and changed her name to courteney cox arquette. but david was a busy boy during the off season for not only did he marry but everyone else as well. for they&#146;re all listed as jennifer aniston arquette, lisa kudrow arquette, in an interesting twist matt leblanc arquette, matthew perry arquette, david schwimmer arquette, and even the creators of the show are now david crane arquette and marta kauffman arquette. i just wonder what the new sleeping arrangements are&#133;}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " why are we in bed together?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. do-do you have any clothes on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  yeah.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " no! but we-we didn&#146;t have&#133;sex-uh, did we? i mean, i don&#146;t remember much about last night, it was such a blur.", "answer": " oh! i remember laughing! i laughed a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " ohh, i mean, we were really drunk. i&#146;m just glad we didn&#146;t do anything stupid.", "answer": "  tell me about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " mornin&#146; pheebs.  well, my movie has officially been canceled.", "answer": " oh joey, i&#146;m so sorry. you want some of my breakfast?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " nah, i&#146;m too depressed to eat. i&#146;ll probably eat in like 5 minutes. so i guess i&#146;ll just fly home with you guys, what time&#146;s your flight?", "answer": " what about my cab?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i don&#146;t need that anymore.", "answer": " no, joey! you borrowed my cab; you have to drive it back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " i don&#146;t want to drive all the way back by myself, i get so lonely.  oh&#151;ooh! how about you come with me?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, it&#146;s such a long trip.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " it&#146;ll be great! we-we could talk, and play games! huh? this could be our chance to like renew our friendship.", "answer": " are you asking me to have a frenaissance?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " sure?", "answer": " all right. although i don&#146;t think we need one, i never stopped loving you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " so, has anyone talked to dr. and mrs. geller yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " um-hmm, yeah. they left me a message; they should be here any minute.", "answer": " where is the waitress?! i&#146;m starving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " it&#146;s a buffet man.", "answer": " oh, here&#146;s where i win all my money back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " listen, i gotta talk to you.", "answer": " sure! what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " monica and i almost got married last night.", "answer": " oh my god! that&#146;s huge!  wait a minute, why come i wasn&#146;t invited? and who was going to be your best man? don&#146;t say, &quot;ross.&quot; do not say, &quot;ross.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " look, i just don&#146;t think monica and i are ready to get married yet! y&#146;know? i mean, i love her and everything but seeing ross and rachel coming out of that chapel was like a, like a wake-up call that monica and i are moving so fast. y&#146;know? and, how do i tell her without crushing her?", "answer": " oh! tell her she&#146;s not marriage material.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " girls say it to me all the time! and believe me, if she&#146;s anything like me, she&#146;s just gonna be relieved.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " how do i tell chandler that it&#146;s too soon. it&#146;s gonna break his heart, he&#146;s not gonna think that i don&#146;t love him anymore.", "answer": " well you don&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yes i do!", "answer": " good! good! i was just testing you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  hi.", "answer": " oh hi! hi! y&#146;know, we were just talking about bacon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " are we gonna talk about what you guys did last night? or&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t know.  what do you mean last night? nothing, nothing uh, happened last night.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " rach! we weren&#146;t gonna miss our friends getting married!", "answer": "  who got married?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  you did.", "answer": " what?! hello! we didn&#146;t get married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " we-we-we&#151;i remember being in a chapel.", "answer": " oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i&#151;they would not let us get married when we were that drunk!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " they let you get married when you&#146;re drunk! most people who get married in vegas are drunk!", "answer": " hell, i&#146;m drunk right now!  what? i can&#146;t have a mimosa with breakfast?! i&#146;m on vacation!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " what are you guys gonna do?", "answer": " well, i guess we just find a divorce lawyer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " well, i think, i think, ross already has one. now, this one&#146;s free, right? because you paid for the first two, so the third one&#146;s free.", "answer": " laugh it up, but the joke&#146;s on you. because we don&#146;t need to get divorced, okay? we we&#146;re just gonna get an annulment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " an annulment? ross! i don&#146;t think surgery&#146;s the answer here.", "answer": " oh-oh, that&#146;s your thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you&#146;re thing. you&#146;re thing. y&#146;know? you&#146;re the guy who gets divorced.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh yeah!", "answer": " no-no, that&#146;s-that&#146;s not my thing! i do not love getting divorced!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " so, what do you think we should do?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. but i-i-i know i love you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " so where are we on the whole going back to the place where they have all the marriages thing? i love you.", "answer": " that&#146;s a good question. look umm, last night we let the dice decide. maybe we should leave it up to fate again. i love you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yes, we don&#146;t get married unless there&#146;s a sign! okay, so say uh, say you roll another eight  then there&#146;s a definite sign that we should get married.", "answer": " all right, eight we get married, but 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 11, 12 we don&#146;t get married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " sounds great.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " coming in, we got a shooter! money please.", "answer": " ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " ready!", "answer": "  come on eight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " wow! i can&#146;t believe i actually rolled an eight.", "answer": " that was so unlikely. well, let&#146;s get married! i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " wait a minute. that wasn&#146;t a hard eight! last night i rolled a hard eight.", "answer": " that&#146;s right! it was the wrong kind of eight, no wedding! damnit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " i wanted it so bad!  wanna go pack?", "answer": " yeah.  we&#146;re doing the right thing, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " okay, you have 19 questions left. use them wisely.  come on joey! you can&#146;t win if you don&#146;t ask any  questions!!!", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " well, you promised me a fun road trip! we&#146;ve been on the road six hours and you&#146;ve been asleep for five and a half! we are switching at the next rest stop and you are going to drive all the way back! that will be your punishment, you greedy sleeper!", "answer": " all right. all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah! and until then you are going to sing to me because the radio&#146;s broken and you are selfish but have a nice voice.", "answer": " really? i don&#146;t&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " sing!!", "answer": "  i wanna rock and roll all night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, hubby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, actually um, i wanted to talk to you about that whole annulment thing?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " okay! so, we&#146;ll just stay married.", "answer": " yes, exactly!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " and i will make everyone call me mrs. geller!", "answer": " wow! this is so amazing. i uh, i really thought i&#146;d have to talk you into this more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay, see now i&#146;m scared because i don&#146;t actually think you&#146;re kidding.", "answer": " i&#146;m-i&#146;m not kidding. look i-i, i can&#146;t have three failed marriages. i can&#146;t. okay? i-i am not gonna be that guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what-wh-what so we&#146;ll just stay married forever?!", "answer": " okay, look, how is this gonna affect you? really? i mean you fill some form out once and a while and instead of checking the box that says ms you check the box that says mrs.! it&#146;s right next to it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " ohh, okay, i&#146;m sorry. you&#146;re right. y&#146;know what? we absolutely can stay married, because i was under the impression that the boxes were far away from each other. all right, look, just please, take a moment here and think about what you&#146;re asking of me.", "answer": " i&#146;m asking you to do me a favor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " does anyone else want to smack ross right about now? raise your hands. okay, put them down before you stink out the person next to you.}", "answer": " you are asking me to be your wife!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " that kid really kicked me hard on the plane.", "answer": " well you did pull his hair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " he took my snack!", "answer": " i&#146;m not getting into this again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " this doesn&#146;t mean anything, does it?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  how could you pick up a hitchhiker?! he could be a rape&#151;, a rapist or a killer or something!", "answer": " don&#146;t you think i asked him that before he got in?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? i&#146;m not talking to you! you go back to sleep!  and you, are you a rapist?!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " do you like car games?", "answer": " yeah, y&#146;know the license plate game?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i love the license plate game!", "answer": " ooh, i&#146;ll play! i&#146;ll play!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " listen, i know you wanted to talk to me, but i have an idea that may make you want to stay married.  we register, and you get to keep all the presents!", "answer": "  no! ross, come on! no! listen, look i thought a lot about how to tell you this and the bottom line, ross, is we can not stay married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know if it&#146;s true.", "answer": " oh b-b-but it is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh, okay, y&#146;know what this is? this is a difference of opinion. and when that happens in a marriage...", "answer": " oh ross, come on! this is not, this is not a marriage!! this is the world&#146;s worst hangover! ross, listen, if you do not get this annulment, i will!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " all right. all right, i&#146;ll do it.", "answer": " thank you.  hey-hey umm, uh, is there, is there any such thing as an annulment shower?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " wait! wait! there is the train station!", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " this is where i get off. well, i have your address and phone number.", "answer": " and i have your name and the fact that you&#146;re a drifter, so the ball&#146;s pretty much in your court.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " come on pheebs! i can&#146;t take this anymore! let-let me make it up to you. huh?  ground control to major tom. commencing countdown, engines on. take your protein pills and put your helmet on!", "answer": " stop it! stop it no! that&#146;s not fair! y&#146;know i can&#146;t resist that beautiful voice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " pheebs, i am so sorry! i know i promised you a fun road trip with your friend and i didn&#146;t deliver. but-but-but now i know that you think being awake is an important part of friendship! so, so, so i will strive to-to stay awake for as long as i know you.", "answer": " you can still sleep at night and stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well, thank you. so, can we play 20 questions now? i&#146;ve got a really good one! i&#146;ve been thinking about it since kansas.", "answer": " okay. is it a kind of hot sandwich?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " is it a meatball sub?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " huh, that&#146;s funny. you look like you&#146;re gonna be the&#133;", "answer": " no, don&#146;t say it! don&#146;t even think it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " all right, should we just, should we just get married? y&#146;know? i mean should we just do it? all the signs are telling us to do it.", "answer": " i&#146;m sick of the signs! it&#146;s too fast, i&#146;m happy the way things are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " me too!", "answer": " i don&#146;t want things to change! do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " all right then, then nothing changes! everything is great! everything stays the same! and you go unpack because it&#146;s been three days and it&#146;s driving me insane!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  y&#146;know i was thinking, what if i uh, unpack here?", "answer": " then all your stuff would be here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " well, what if all my stuff was here?", "answer": " then you&#146;d be going back and forth all the time, i mean it doesn&#146;t make any sense.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " okay. what if we lived together and you understand what i&#146;m saying?", "answer": " live together? there have been no signs for that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " me asking is kind of a sign.", "answer": " yes!!!!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yes! okay! okay! wait-wait-wait!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh thanks.", "answer": " here&#146;s your key. all right, you have to christen it! now, go out and come back in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " the door hasn&#146;t been locked in five years, but okay!  ready?!", "answer": " ready!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay, a little problem. the key broke in the lock and i can&#146;t get", "answer": " wait! oh my god! i can&#146;t get out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " this is not a sign!", "answer": " no, it&#146;s not a sign! it&#146;s a very old key!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " it&#146;s an old key!", "answer": " oh my god it&#146;s old!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i love you!", "answer": " i love you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " yeah-yeah, me neither.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, so did everything go all right with the annulment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh, yeah, no problems. it&#146;s all taken care of.", "answer": " ross, thank you. hey, do you guys wanna go see a movie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oh yeah, why not?", "answer": " pheebs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no thanks, i&#146;ve already seen one.", "answer": " okay, umm, i&#146;m gonna get my sweater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " okay.  you uh, you wanna hear something weird?", "answer": " always.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t get the annulment.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " the key&#146;s stuck in the lock.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  it still doesn&#146;t work.", "answer": " i&#146;m not finished.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}]